C: 609-865-8031

Email: ambliach@gmail.com

Summary

Human Resource Management and Philosophy double major adept and experienced in project management, strategic full life cycle recruiting & problem solving. Proven to be efficient, enthusiastic, and versatile with strong professional communication, leadership, and analytical skills.

Work Experience

HR Manager

08/2016-Present

Always Best Care Senior Services

- Created successful targeted strategy for recruiting home health aides in key areas positively impacting retention rate resulting in a consistent talent pool
- Screened, interviewed and on-boarded more than 300 new employees
- Integral team member of a 3-million-dollar start-up with 20% year-on-year growth
- Assisted executives with 3rd party clinical accreditation and assisted and managed compliance policies and procedures with a 3-month implementation window for outside audit resulting in 100 percent pass in all audits
- Trained and directed interns to support local community involvement and provide clerical support
- Marketed to local community centers, churches, temples, mosques leveraging more referrals and prospective employees
- Managed key client relationships through consistent outreach and strategic visits
- Maintained all agency licenses through monitored compliance with the New Jersey Board of Nursing
- Recruited and directed students through NJ Board of Nursing approved Home Health Aide certification class in order to introduce new pools of employees
- On-boarded & interviewed all new employees
- Created work description for HR coordinator/office manager positions providing company with standard operating procedure for various processes
- Conducted in-service orientations resulting in increased employee retention
- Implemented several employee award incentives to drive employee referrals & retention
- · Managed all agency policies, procedures & manuals
- Migration and management of two payroll systems (ADP/Viventium)
- Automated onboarding process reducing errors, improving compliance and streamlining process
- Ongoing project creating unique program for insurance activity reporting, client/caregiver communication and caregiver clocking-in system all through one application

Recruiting Intern 5/2016-7/2016

Lorelei Staffing

- Screened and interviewed candidates for direct hire, contract, and contract-to hire opportunities
- Communicated with clients in a fast-paced, deadline driven environment
- · Worked independently and as a team to foster professional growth for both candidates and clients

Retail Manager 11/2014-05/2016

Marin Pharmacy

- Assisted and resolved various client issues leading to 100 % costumer satisfaction
- Managed data for insurance reclaims to ensure total accuracy of pharmacy revenue
- Managed and ensured prop
- · er medication rotation achieving complete accuracy with annual state audits
- Responsible for insurance filing and compliance

Education

Trilogy Education through Rutgers University
Full Stack MERN Web Development Coding Bootcamp

August 2019

Rutgers, The State University of New Jersey, New Brunswick, NJ B.A. in Philosophy and Human Resource Management (Double Major)

May, 2016

Skills		
☐ Full cycle recruitment ☐	Viventium Payroll	Spanish
■ ADP Workforce Now	software	(conversational)
	Paychex Flex	